fare-finder.com 2018-06-08

# Privacy Policy - Fare-Finder.com

**Privacy Policy**

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the fare-finder.com and Fare-Finder.com and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Fare-Finder.com include fare-finder.com. The Fare-Finder.com website is a Travel Discount Comparison site. By using the Fare-Finder.com website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information**

Fare-Finder.com may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Fare-Finder.com. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Fare-Finder.com website.

Fare-Finder.com encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Fare-Finder.com so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Fare-Finder.com is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Fare-Finder.com website.

**Use of your Personal Information**

Fare-Finder.com collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

Fare-Finder.com may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Fare-Finder.com and its affiliates. Fare-Finder.com may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Fare-Finder.com does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Fare-Finder.com may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. Fare-Finder.com may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Fare-Finder.com, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Fare-Finder.com may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Fare-Finder.com, in order to determine what Fare-Finder.com services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Fare-Finder.com to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Fare-Finder.com will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Fare-Finder.com or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Fare-Finder.com; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Fare-Finder.com, or the public.

**Use of Cookies**

The Fare-Finder.com website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Fare-Finder.com pages, or register with Fare-Finder.com site or services, a cookie helps Fare-Finder.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Fare-Finder.com website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Fare-Finder.com features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Fare-Finder.com services or websites you visit.

**Security of your Personal Information**

Fare-Finder.com secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

**Children Under Thirteen**

Fare-Finder.com does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

**Opt-Out & Unsubscribe**

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Fare-Finder.com by contacting us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#f29b9c949db294938097df949b9c969780dc919d9f)

**Changes to this Statement**

Fare-Finder.com will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Fare-Finder.com encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Fare-Finder.com is protecting your information.

**Contact Information**

Fare-Finder.com welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Fare-Finder.com has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Fare-Finder.com at:

201 N Brand Blvd  
Glendale, CA 91203  
[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  
213-536-9516 

Effective as of March 13, 2017
